More of a hindrance than a help.
إنه عائق أكثر من كونه مساعدة.
Master.
يتقن.
Please forgive me this time.
أرجوك أن تسامحني هذه المرة.
For the sake of
من أجل
Yanzhi serving you for so long.
لقد خدمتك يانزهي لفترة طويلة.
Get out.
اخرج.
You're useless now.
أنت عديم الفائدة الآن.
Master.
يتقن.
I beg you, Master.
أتوسل إليك يا سيدي.
Leave.
يترك.
Since you're here,
بما أنك هنا،
why are you hiding?
لماذا انت مختبئ؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
What are you here for?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Master Fu, your cultivation is impressive.
سيد فو، زراعتك مثيرة للإعجاب.
I am a Spiritual Cultivator.
أنا مزارع روحي.
I'm here to sell spiritual power-enhancing medicines.
أنا هنا لبيع الأدوية المعززة للقوة الروحية.
Such medicines always have side effects.
مثل هذه الأدوية لها دائمًا آثار جانبية.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
I'm a fool?
أنا أحمق؟
With the current situation,
مع الوضع الحالي،
the three great families plus Chen Yuanqi
العائلات الثلاث الكبرى بالإضافة إلى تشين يوانكي
are not easy to deal with.
ليس من السهل التعامل معها.
Why not take a look at my goods first?
لماذا لا تقوم بإلقاء نظرة على بضاعتي أولاً؟
Every deal comes with a price.
كل صفقة لها ثمن.
But I don't believe
ولكنني لا أصدق
you won't be tempted.
لن تتعرض للإغراء.
Here it comes!
هنا يأتي!
The last dish.
الطبق الأخير.
Brother Yuanqi, you're amazing!
الأخ يوانكي، أنت مدهش!
These are my specialty dishes.
هذه هي أطباقي المتخصصة.
Can I sneak a bite?
هل يمكنني أن أتناول قضمة؟
I've been holding back for so long.
لقد كنت متردداً لفترة طويلة.
How does it taste?
كيف طعمها؟
It smells so good!
رائحتها طيبة للغاية!
Brother Yuanqi, you're the best!
الأخ يوانكي، أنت الأفضل!
You're back!
لقد عدت!
I've been waiting for you.
لقد كنت في انتظارك.
Come on, sit down quickly!
هيا اجلس بسرعة!
I've waited so long, sit down!
لقد انتظرت طويلاً، اجلس!
Congratulations, little champion!
مبروك يا بطل الصغير!
Try my cooking.
جرب طبخي.
To celebrate my success in the medical exam.
للاحتفال بنجاحي في الامتحان الطبي.
Brother Yuanqi.
الأخ يوانكي.
I believe you can do it.
أعتقد أنك قادر على فعل ذلك.
You'll win the next championship too.
وسوف تفوز بالبطولة القادمة أيضًا.
Alright, wait for my victory.
حسنًا، انتظر انتصاري.
I'll ask the righteous to help find your other clansmen.
سأطلب من الصالحين مساعدتك في العثور على أفراد عشيرتك الآخرين.
Brother Yuanqi.
الأخ يوانكي.
You're so good to me.
أنت جيد جدًا معي.
Sister Lie.
الأخت لي.
When Brother Yuanqi becomes the Righteous Alliance Leader,
عندما أصبح الأخ يوانكي زعيم التحالف الصالح،
what do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
I don't have time to daydream with you two.
ليس لدي وقت للحلم معكما.
Don't disturb my meal.
لا تزعج وجبتي.
All you care about is eating!
كل ما يهمك هو الأكل!
Brother Yuanqi's cooking is delicious, right?
طبخ الأخ يوانكي لذيذ، أليس كذلك؟
I wish we could always be like this.
أتمنى أن نكون دائمًا هكذا.
And with Sister Yumeng too.
ومع الأخت يومينغ أيضًا.
I hope we can always be together.
أتمنى أن نكون معًا دائمًا.
Eat and play together till old age.
تناولوا الطعام واللعب معًا حتى الكبر.
Sure!
بالتأكيد!
When that time comes,
عندما يأتي ذلك الوقت،
I'll cook for you every day.
سأطبخ لك كل يوم.
Is it really that blissful?
هل هو حقا بهذه السعادة؟
Here, try this one too.
هنا، حاول هذا أيضًا.
Thank you, Brother Yuanqi.
شكرا لك أخي يوانكي.
Here, you try it too.
هنا، يمكنك تجربتها أيضًا.
It's so tasty!
إنه لذيذ جداً!
Today's dishes are much better than before.
أطباق اليوم أفضل بكثير من ذي قبل.
Everything tastes great.
كل شيء له طعم رائع.
You should eat more too.
ينبغي عليك أن تأكل أكثر أيضاً.
Eat more!
تناول المزيد!
Training is tough.
التدريب صعب.
Lie Shumei.
كذب شومي.
Kneel and receive orders.
اركع وتلقى الأوامر.
I didn't expect you to be the Holy Envoy of the Cult Leader.
لم أتوقع أن تكون المبعوث المقدس لزعيم الطائفة.
Please give your orders, Holy Envoy.
من فضلك أعط أوامرك، أيها المبعوث المقدس.
I want you to atone for your mistakes.
أريدك أن تكفر عن أخطائك.
Use this packet of Gu Powder
استخدم هذه العبوة من مسحوق Gu
on Chen Yuanqi.
على تشين يوانكي.
He will become my complete puppet.
سيصبح دميتي الكاملة.
Forgive me, Holy Envoy.
سامحني أيها المبعوث المقدس.
I'm now Chen Yuanqi's Sword Spirit.
أنا الآن روح سيف تشين يوانكي.
I can't harm my host.
لا أستطيع أن أؤذي مضيفى.
This method
هذه الطريقة
can free you from the Sword Spirit's restraints.
يمكنه تحريرك من قيود روح السيف.
But Chen Yuanqi has divine protection.
لكن تشين يوانكي يتمتع بالحماية الإلهية.
He's immune to all poisons.
فهو محصن ضد جميع السموم.
I'm afraid I...
أخشى أنني...
No matter.
لا يهم.
This is a Gu insect, not poison.
هذه حشرة جو، وليست سمًا.
It can make Chen Yuanqi lose all his power at a critical moment.
قد يؤدي ذلك إلى فقدان تشين يوانكي كل قوته في لحظة حرجة.
Lie Shumei.
كذب شومي.
Have you forgotten the price of defying the Cult Leader?
هل نسيت ثمن تحدي زعيم الطائفة؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I...
أنا...
I have no choice.
ليس لدي خيار.
Why?
لماذا؟
Why is this happening?
لماذا يحدث هذا؟
I tried so hard.
لقد حاولت جاهدا.
I just wanted to rise from obscurity to prominence.
لقد أردت فقط أن أرتفع من الغموض إلى الشهرة.
What did I do wrong?
ماذا فعلت خطأ؟
Fu Cangtian.
فو كانغتيان.
I've served you so many times.
لقد خدمتك عدة مرات.
And yet you just cast me out like this.
ومع ذلك طردتني بهذه الطريقة.
What did I do to deserve this?
ماذا فعلت لأستحق هذا؟
It's not your fault.
إنه ليس خطؤك.
Who?
من؟
Someone who can give you everything.
شخص يمكنه أن يعطيك كل شيء.
The Seven Meridians Championship, the martial arts competition begins.
بدأت بطولة السبع خطوط الطول، منافسات الفنون القتالية.
I don't know where Sister Lie went.
لا أعلم أين ذهبت الأخت لاي.
I'm really worried about her.
أنا قلق عليها حقا.
Isn't she your Sword Spirit?
أليست هي روح السيف الخاصة بك؟
How could she leave the Chiyou Sword?
كيف يمكنها أن تترك سيف تشييو؟
I don't know either.
انا أيضا لا اعرف.
Will she come back?
هل ستعود؟
If she truly insists on leaving,
إذا أصرت حقا على المغادرة،
I can't force her to stay.
لا أستطيع إجبارها على البقاء.
First round of the competition.
الجولة الأولى من المسابقة.
Ye Xuan from Divine Sword Manor.
يي شوان من قصر السيف الإلهي.
Versus Chen Yuanqi from the humble clan.
مقابل تشين يوانكي من العشيرة المتواضعة.
Brother Yuanqi, what's wrong?
الأخ يوانكي، ما الأمر؟
It's nothing.
لا شئ.
Go, Brother Yuanqi!
إذهب يا أخي يوانكي!
I believe in you.
إنني أ ثق بك.
Ye Xuan, head of the Ye family at Divine Sword Manor.
يي شوان، رئيس عائلة يي في قصر السيف الإلهي.
Ye Xuan, master of Innate Sword Qi.
يي شوان، سيد تشي السيف الفطري.
Oh no.
أوه لا.
How did Brother Yuanqi end up facing him?
كيف انتهى الأمر بالأخ يوانكي بمواجهته؟
Why are you boosting his morale and doubting yourself?
لماذا ترفع معنوياته وتشكك في نفسك؟
Brother Yuanqi can't possibly lose!
من غير الممكن أن يخسر الأخ يوانكي!
My Sword Qi...
سيفي تشي...
Lethal in ten paces.
قاتل في عشر خطوات.
I'll strike three times.
سأضرب ثلاث مرات.
If you survive,
إذا نجوت،
I'll spare your life.
سأنقذ حياتك.
Do noble families always boast so much?
هل تفتخر العائلات النبيلة دائمًا بهذا القدر؟
First strike—Sword Qi spans ninety thousand miles!
الضربة الأولى - سيف تشي يمتد لمسافة تسعين ألف ميل!
No, why is my Phoenix Flame Eternal sealed?
لا، لماذا تم ختم شعلة الفينيق الأبدية الخاصة بي؟